

ADITHYA VARDHAN

Functional Consultant, SAP PM, CS & FSM - Hyderabad, India.

Phone: +91 9553223682, E-mail: adithya.pav003@gmail.com

Overview

SAP professional with **8+ years** of experience as a consultant as well as end user across various industries such as **Power plants**, **GAS (PNG, CNG)**, **Dairy Units** & **Tyre manufacturing**. Strong industrial domain experience helped me to understand the client business process quickly and deliver the best configurations.

Total experience: 8 yrs. 01 months.

- B-Tech in Electrical Engineering from Institution of Engineers India IEI, Kolkata.
- Successfully delivered 2 Implementation, 2 Rollout and 5 Support projects.
- SAP PM, CS & FSM functional consultant with very good command of SAP ECC & S/4 HANA.
- Expert in configuring Master Data & Transactional Data. Implementation & supporting all phases of a project life
 cycle including analysis, configuration, testing and deployment of Maintenance & Service Business
 Processes and solutions, post-production support/maintenance, documentation, and end-user training.
- · Good communication skills & strong leadership qualities.
- Good command of Unit Testing, System Integration testing, Regression Testing.
- Expertise in Preventive Maintenance, Breakdown Maintenance, Refurbishment processing, Calibration order, Investment order & Service orders.
- Competent in Data migration from legacy to SAP system using Legacy System Migration Workbench LSMW,
 LTMC.

With the above skills also have good knowledge of other functional modules like MM, PS & DMS. Technical modules like ABAP (can code ALV's, Module Pools, User Exit, Customer Exit, Forms & Enhancements Etc...)

SAP PM/CS Technicalities

Organization Structure **Maintenance Notification** Refurbishment Maintenance **Maintenance Order Calibration Process Functional Location** MIC's **Equipment master** Task List **Bill Of Materials** Maintenance Plans **Investment Order** Investment Measure & Profile Work Center Scheduling Class & Characteristics

Deadline Monitoring
Background Job Scheduling
Fleet Management
Tool Management

Service Order & Notifications
Service calls and activities
Maintenance & Service Reporting
Work Clearance Management

Gemini

Experience & Projects

Revision

Software:

Gemini Consulting and Services India Ltd.

Measurement Point / Documents

DMS Master Data attachments

Job title: Consultant – SAP PM (Jan 2022 to Present)

SAP ECC6 and S4 HANA

Projects: Central U.P Gas Limited. (Implementation)

COMFED—Bihar State Co Operative Milk Federation. (Implementation & Rollout)

Rajasthan Rajya Vidyut Prasaran Nigam Limited. (Support)
SJVNL, Shimla (Support)
Rezayat Group – Saudi Arabia. (SAP CS, FSM & DMS) (Support)



PROJECT NAME:	Central U.P Gas Limited - Gas Project
PROJECT TYPE	SAP IMPLEMENATATION S/4 HANA - PM Module
DURATION	From Jan 2022 to Aug 2022
ROLES& RESPONSIBILITY	 Implemented WCM Process which is very crucial for Oil and Gas organization. Configured and created PM Master Data - Functional Locations, Equipment's, and Material BOMs, Work Centers, Class & Characteristic, catalogue, code group & code for better breakdown classification, measuring documents & point for equipment history, trends. Created General Maintenance Task Lists for inspection, maintenance and repair processes of equipment's and used these task lists for Preventive Maintenance instead of creating individual Equipment Task Lists. Preventive Maintenance - performed necessary configuration for creating time-based and performance-based maintenance plans, scheduled maintenance plans for defined cycles to generate maintenance calls and processing of maintenance calls. Measurement documents were used to evaluate equipment by using measuring points and counters. Configuration of Notifications and work order. Refurbishment of repairable spares, Processing of external services, Calibration Order process, Sub-order, Shut-down maintenance order. Configured Completion Confirmation of Maintenance and Service Order processing - defined control parameters, set up screen templates and field selection. Performed data migration from Legacy system to SAP Plant Maintenance tables using Legacy System Migration Workbench (LSMW). Created purchase order in MM, received goods and performed the post goods movement for order processing for testing purpose. Created detailed documentation, trained end users, and provided post implementation support. Involved in different phases such as business requirement collection AS-IS, TO-BE process, Business blueprint, configuration, testing, user training, go live, and post implementation support.

PROJECT NAME:	COMFED - Bihar State Co Operative Milk Federation		
PROJECT TTPE	SAP Implementation & Rollout ECC 6.0 – PM Module		
DURATION	From Aug 2022 to Present		
ROLES& RESPONSIBILITY	 Understanding the Business processes of Client & mapping those with SAP. Preparation of AS-IS and TO-BE documents, Business Blueprint & KDS Documents Etc. If GAP is found, then prepare FS documents & connect with ABAP team. Configurations of various Master data and transactional data of PM Module. SAP PM Integrations with other modules like MM, QM, FICO etc. Testing of developed requirements by using various testing methods. Handling Training Sessions to the end users and preparations of manuals. Handling different Incidents, SR's and CR's of other support projects. Planning & execution of PM schedule, Corrective maintenance for various equipment for optimum availability of equipment. Mapping of annual Maintenance plan to SAP PM single cycle maintenanceplan, Strategy cycle Maintenance plan by assigning Equipment Task List and General Task List, Measuring points counter. Prepared end user Self-Help documentation with detailed steps andscreen shots for all the daily based T-codes. 		



PROJECT NAME	REZAYAT -	Rezayat Group – Saudi Arabia
PROJECT TYPE	SAP Support Project	t S/4 Hana _ CS_FSM & DMS Mo

PROJECT TYPE	SAP Support Project S/4 Hana - CS, FSM & DMS Module
DURATION	From Jun 2023 to Present
ROLES & RESPONSIBILITY	 Handling CR's & SR's Handling Incedents thourgh ITSM and Fastract CR's Support end user in Planning & execution of preventive schedule. Handling service orders with FSM SAP Enable Now documents preparation. Conducting UAT through HP ALM and TRQ preparations Etc. FSM Configurations like Equipments, Functional locations, Users, Materials, Service calls, Activities and Work Time Etc. Cockpit monitoring to check inbounds and outbounds DMS configurations like document types, version management, strucutring, distributions and reports management with class. Etc SAP training for end users for optimum utilization of SAP. Attend Status Call every week with business and management.

MRF Ltd.

Job title: Junior Officer – SAP PM (May 2020 to Aug 2021)

Software: SAP ECC6

Project: MRF Limited (Rollout)
MRF AKMA (Support)

PROJECT NAME MRF Limited & MRF AKMA

PROJECT TYPE	SAP Rollout & Support Project ECC 6.0 – PM Module		
DURATION	From May 2020 to Aug 2021		
ROLES & RESPONSIBILITY	 Roll out activities of SAP PM Module for MRF Dahej plant. Support to all manufacturing plants (10 plants), Handling Tickets. Development of all processes within SAP - architecture as well as the development of new solutions. Reduce offline procedures and mapping with them into SAP. Analysis of whole PM module and validate where the system lags. Configurations and creation of various Master data and transactional data. Day-to-day analysis and updating reports. RCA, Breakdown, CAPA reports & other various reports are developed. Preparing function design documents for all technical objects and master data Preparing RICEFW design documents for new reequipments Configuring all KDS, master data, notification, orders Planning & tagging the project activities in agile methodology. SAP PM training for end user for optimum utilization of SAP Preparing authorization role matrix for PM user per client requirements. Attend Status Call every week with business and management. Configure all PM related Nodes. Integration part with all modules. conducting workshops and requirements analysis to help the client understand the various deployment approaches. Data Loads using LSMW etc. 		



Experience summary

SAP Consultant Experience:

6 Gemini Consulting and Services SAP PM Consultant (Jan2022 to Present) 2Yrs. 8 Months. **4 MRF Ltd** Jr. Officer SAP PM (May 2020 to Aug 2021) 1Yr 4 Months

Total Experience includes Plant Maintenance Domain & SAP PM End User

6 Gemini Consulting and Services SAP PM Consultant (Jan2022 to Present)

5 KIA India pvt Ltd. Automation mainenance Engieer (Aug2021 to Oct 2021)

4 MRF Ltd Jr. Officer SAP PM (May 2020 to Aug 2021)

3 Flextronics Tech. India Pvt Ltd. Automation maintenance Engineer (Dec 2019 to March 2020)
2 Molex India Pvt Ltd. End User SAP & Equipment maintenance (April 2019 to Nov 2019)
1 Rakon India Pvt Ltd. End User SAP & Equipment maintenance (Jun 2016 to April 2019)

Software skills

• SAP ECC6 and S4 HANA – SAP PM, CS & FSM, also have good knowledge on MM, PS, DMS too.

- SAP ABAP Code & Debugging, Module pool, ALV, Forms.
- PLC programming languages LD, FBD, ST.
- Well acquainted with HMI and SCADA programming and design.
- Proficient in designing software (E CAD, AE).

Career highlights

- Appreciation: Received Appreciation from RVPNL Project for Customizing and Configuring the best in PM module to make the process easy.
- Appreciation: Received appreciation from COMFED for implementing and shorting of all the

pending issues, after project restart.

Received Best Kaizen award & EOY from RAKON.

Personality skills

Awards:

- Strong communication skills can be able to handle the clients with better understanding.
- Attention to details with patience. Strong Leadership qualities and teamwork attributes.
- Strong problem solving and interpersonal communication skills.
- Able to work in large teams contributing expertise and suggestions for efficient execution of projects.
- Ability to effectively communicate at multiple levels in the organization.
- Able to Handle stressful situations and work with whole-hearted dedication to achieve desired results in time.

Educational credentials

• BE in Electrical & Electronics EngineeringIEI, Kolkata (Institution of engineers India).

• Diploma in Electrical & Electronics Engineering Swamy Vivekananda Polytechnic (SVP), Bobbili, Andhra Pradesh.

Personal credentials

Full Name: Parasurampuram Adithya Vardhan.

Address: Flat No. F1 Venu Nivas – 3, Kalighat Colony, Vizianagaram, Andhra Pradesh. 535003.

Languages: English, Hindi, Telugu, Kannada.

Date of birth: 26th June 1998. Hobbies: Photography & Music.

Nationality: Indian. Passport: Yes.